Young people who don't trust him for
us as a first person.
Karine, GDPR, how dare you talk about-
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
You are the Arby's head to the genocide in Gaza.
Get it.
Two years you set up on saying a lot to the American public.
How dare you try to claim that you're independent.
Talk about the Holocaust of the Palestinian people.
Yep.
You're a human being.
You, you were a human being.
Tell her.
May she never know people.
Karine, you are going on stage every day and
you're going to justify a genocide.
That is your legacy, that will forever be your legacy.
Shame on you, shame, shame, shame on you.
You said a couple of days ago that you were very proud-
Okay.
Nothing back from what you did in that administration.
And you just talked about crises, I was sitting here listening.
And you failed to mention the genocide that you have talked about,
day after day to cover up.
Okay.
So I want to ask you, are you ashamed or are you proud of the way that this administration
should all of you have brought up on your hand?
Let me tell you something else.
I am not the policy.
Wrong answer.
Her, Matt Miller, Kamala Harris, all of them who sat up every single day, Joe Biden, and lied.
Bad, bold-faced, lied, in order to be complicit in the genocide against Palestinians should
never know a day of peace.
These people have continuously made it their business to advance the effort of Zionism,
which we all know is an incredible threat to the peace and prosperity of anyone everywhere.
And they want to sit up here and say things like, I'm not a policymaker.
Ma'am, you are a policy perpetuator.
And that makes you an enabler.
And that makes you an accomplice.
Now, look at this.
Now, here we have NYC's fire commissioner resigning because he doesn't agree with Mamdani's
stance on Israel.
Now, this is some BS.
But you see what it looks like to resign for your beliefs?
Disguster.
Engaging in the expansion of empire is not a job.
It's actually a choice.
You know, people always say the old adage, life is short.
But no, life is long and your choices follow you every step of the way.
And one that someone who was getting the paycheck she had, had every ability to walk away from.
I hope that her, Kamala, Matt Miller, and the rest of these liars, I hope every day for
them is one of haunting.
And I hope their sleeves get wet every time they wash their hands.
Because they'll never be able to get the blood off.
Sister Seals, this is your ancestor, Harriet Tubman.
I am Clarence Tubman!